<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on 7risten</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on 7risten</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:02:21 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Designing Better Applications at the Expense of User Autonomy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/designing-better-applications-at-the-expense-of-user-autonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:02:21 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/designing-better-applications-at-the-expense-of-user-autonomy/</guid>
      <description>some cases maybe you can produce better apps by taking options out of the end users hands autonomous vehicles. offering opportunity&amp;rsquo;s for customization can be good can also create bulnerabillitys points of failure what should compute professional goal? to enhance autonomy by making choice available or constraining them.&#xA;t.s. (start with conclusion) since p1 p2 pn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professionalism in Computing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/professionalism-in-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:29:42 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/professionalism-in-computing/</guid>
      <description>t.s. (start with conclusion) since p1 p2 pn&#xA;should coputing be a regulated licenced profession.&#xA;would have effect that only well qualified people do the work.&#xA;if high concequence&#xA;if put in place then form of market exclusion&#xA;deprived of useful technology&#xA;separate domain by consequence social medial, gaming, regulator mush anticipate&#xA;criminal civil penalties (after the fact) regulation (playing catch up, anticipating) proff licensing (cost innovation higher cost) proff regulation (even not legally required maybe useful if you thought of yourself)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Simplicity in Web Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-value-of-simplicity-in-web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-value-of-simplicity-in-web-development/</guid>
      <description>Sacrilege If I have to listen to one more person arguing about which text editor is better, or why some programming language is inferior, I will seriously consider becoming a plumber. At least I doubt I will have to suffer any arguments about which type of toilet is better at flushing excrement; which will be a relief after having to listen to so much of it.&#xA;Vanilla But seriously, I&amp;rsquo;m aghast at how badly some educated, intelligent people entirely miss the point.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
